apkdownloadforwindows.com 2019-10-29

# Privacy Policy

Last Updated: December 19, 2017

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at **info@apkdownloadforwindows.com**

At **apkdownloadforwindows.com** , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by **apkdownloadforwindows.com** and how it is used.

 **Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, **apkdownloadforwindows.com** makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies**

 **apkdownloadforwindows.com** does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

 **Google/DoubleClick DART Cookie/Information Collection**

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to **apkdownloadforwindows.com** or other websites.

Google’s use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to **apkdownloadforwindows.com** and/or other sites on the Internet.

You may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). (Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).)

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on our website send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

 **apkdownloadforwindows.com** and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report how ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our website.

 **apkdownloadforwindows.com** has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. **apkdownloadforwindows.com** privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
